Selected Cancel / Button / ControlType.Pane / 2
Native dialog verified: Open Fig backup
Selected Open / Button / ControlType.Pane / 1
Native dialog verified: Open Fig backup
Selected Open / Button / ControlType.Pane / 1
Native dialog verified: Open Fig backup
Selected Open / Button / ControlType.Pane / 1
Native dialog verified: Import contacts (.vcf)
Selected Save / Button / ControlType.Pane / 1
Native dialog verified: Export XML
[
  'Open Fig backup displays actual Windows picker; Cancel works',
  'Welcome button imports using actual Windows picker',
  'Open Fig backup imports a ZIP using the actual Windows picker',
  'Native contact file selection',
  'Native Save XML dialog writes correct file',
  'Full application restart restores messages and contact names'
]
